(applause, cheering
and whooping)
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Can he really
throw a ball?
(Leonard:)On our Quidditch
team, he...
Yeah, that's a "no."
(Howard:)I have a message
for the young people here today.
(Howard:)When I was asked
to throw the first pitch,
(Howard:)a little voice in my head said
I couldn't do it.
(Howard:)So, I practiced and practiced,
(Howard:)and you know what?
That little voice... (laughs)
(Howard:)...was right, but...
(Howard:)...then I remembered
that I'm not an athlete.
(Howard:)I'm a scientist.
(Howard:)So, today's
(Howard:)first pitch will be delivered
(Howard:)to home plate by science.
(Stadium Announcer:)Ladies and gentlemen,
(Howard:)boys and girls, I present to you
(Howard:)a working prototype
of the Mars Rover!